Career Summary

Software Developer with 6 year of experience in Analysis, Design and Development of native - hybrid Mobile Apps (Android/ IOS) with Knowledge on development of video games 2D / 3D. Agile Methodologies: Scrum, technologies: (KOTLIN, Android Jetpack Compose, JAVA, FLUTTER, SWIFT, JavaScript, React, HTML5, CSS, SQL, C#). Bachelor degree in systems engineering.

Main projects worked on:

- Play Disney App, technology Android(kotlin)
- Todo Pago Apps, technology Android(kotlin/JAVA)
- Credibanco App, technology Android(kotlin)
- InproextApp for Inproext SAS, technology Flutter (Android/IOS)
- Movies Library DB, technology Flutter (Android/IOS)
- ActpolApp for acts curacao, technology Android (Kotlin)
- Justo & Bueno App for panama, technology Flutter (Android/IOS)
- Latte App for TOSTAO, technology Android (Java)
- Horneo App for TOSTAO, technology Android (Java)
- Loteria virtual App for Datacenter (Paga Todo), technology Android (Java)
- Vendedor App for Datacenter (Paga Todo), technology Android (Kotlin)
- Mobile Web services and Android Web Applications for Ejercito/Policia de colombia, technology Java

Summary of Qualifications

Skills:

Native Mobile
Development
Kotlin
Android
Flutter

Languages

Spanish (native speaker)
English (advanced)

Career History

Acid Labs , Remote Work

September 2022 – Currently

Android Mobile Developer

Analysis, Design and Development of Android mobile applications - Clean and Modular Architecture,
Jetpack Compose, Navigation components, Hilt Dagger dependency injection

Globant, Bogota, Colombia

Feb. 2021 – July 2022

Android Mobile Developer

Analysis, Design and Development of Android mobile applications - Clean and Modular Architecture,

ROOM, Navigation components, Jetpack Compose, Koin and Dagger dependency injection

Asesoftware, Bogota, Colombia

Mobile Developer

Analysis, Design and Development of Android mobile applications- MVP Architecture, sqllite database

Flutter Mobile Developer

Jul. 2020 – Aug. 2020

Aug. 2020 - Feb. 2021

Analysis, Design and Development of hybrid mobile applications - Bloc Architecture with providers

Mobile Developer

Feb. 2020 – Jul. 2020

 Analysis, Design and Development of mobile applications Android - MVC, MVVMi Architecture, sqllite database, Dagger

Mobile Developer

May. 2019 – Feb. 2020

 Maintenance and Development of mobile applications Android / IOS - MVC, MVVMi Architecture, sqllite database

Systems Analyst

Apr. 2019 – May. 2019

• Maintenance and Development of Web Applications

May. 2018 – Oct. 2018

Universidad Manuela Beltran, Bogota, Colombia Software Engineer

• Analysis, Design and Development of web applications

Sinte Soluciones SAS, Bogotá, Colombia

Jul. 2017 – May. 2018

Analyst Developer

- Analysis, Design and Development of Android and web applications with Web Services -MVC Architecture.
- Analyze and study existing systems to carry out proposals for improvement
- Propose and develop, based on the systems analysed, improvement options to them, which guarantee better results for the client
- Attend and actively participate in the meetings held on the project under development, to involve the necessary improvements to the system entrusted to the company
- Receive the general guidelines for design and specifications of the solution from the Software Architect

Fundacion Tecnologica Colombo Germana, Bogotá, Colombia

Mar. 2016 – May. 2017

Programmer e-learning

- Developer of Web applications for the management of the internal processes of the university in the e-learning area
- Database management: MySQL and PostgreSQL

Jazzplat Colombia, Bogotá, Colombia

Jul. 2015 - Jan. 2016

Programmer

- Development of trivia programs required by the company
- Database management: MySQL and PostgreSQL

Education

Politécnico Grancolombiano, Bogotá, Colombia

Jan. 2016 - Mar. 2018

Systems Engineering

SENA, Bogota, Colombia

Jan. 2014 - Jan. 2016

Associate Degree in Analysis and Development of information systems References

Name: Nick Badal

Position: Lead Software Engineer at The Walt Disney Company email:

badalnick@gmail.com

Name: West Fort

Position: Lead Software Engineer at The Walt Disney Company email:

fortwest@gmail.com

Name: Cuauhtémoc Pascacio

Position: Android Developer at Globant email: pascaciorc@gmail.com

Name: Rafael Bermudez

Position: Android Developer at Globant email: rafalex.berm@gmail.com

Name: Jhonatan Cuesta Sanchez

Position: Software Engineer at Mercado Libre

email: jonathancuesta97@gmail.com

Name: Juan Fernando Castro

Position: Software Architect at Simetrik email: juanfercas2002@gmail.com Name:

Diego Marin

Position: IOS App Developer at Mercado Libre

Telephone: 3165202818

Name: Jair Londoño

Position: Technical Lead at Asesoftware email: jlondono@asesoftware.com

Name: Lex Duran Soto

Position: Technical Architect at PGD Latam

Telephone: 3173577545

Abel Felipe Chaux Gutiérrez C.C. No. 1012437630